http://www.securemac.com/privacy#donotsell

Privacy Policy1. PurposeThis Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the SecureMac EULA End User License Agreement (the “Terms”). The terms “SecureMac,” “we,” and “us” include SecureMac, Inc. and our affiliates and subsidiaries. This Privacy Policy describes the information we may collect, how we intend to use and share that information, and how you can opt-out of a use or correct or change such information. All other terms not defined in Section 13 or otherwise herein will have the meanings set forth in the Terms.2. ScopeThis Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information that is Processed by SecureMac in the course of our business, including on SecureMac websites and social media sites (each a “Site”), mobile applications, blogs, and other online or offline offerings (collectively, the “Services”). All individuals whose responsibilities include the Processing of Personal Information on behalf of SecureMac are expected to protect that data by adherence to this Privacy Policy. 3. TRANSPARENCY/NOTICE—TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE ITThe types of Personal Information we may collect (directly from you or from Third-Party sources) and our privacy practices depend on the nature of the relationship you have with SecureMac and the requirements of applicable law. Some of the ways that SecureMac may collect Personal Information include:You may provide Personal Information directly to SecureMac through interacting with the Site, purchasing our products, and requesting Services or information.As you navigate the Site and the Services, certain passive information may also be collected about your visit, including through cookies and similar technologies as described below.We endeavor to collect only that information which is relevant for the purposes of Processing. Below are the ways we collect Personal Information and how we use it.1. Types of Personal Information We CollectSecureMac collects Personal Information regarding its current, prospective, and former clients, customers, users, visitors, guests, and Employees (collectively “Individuals”).Information You Provide Directly to Us. When you use the Services or engage in certain activities with SecureMac, such as purchasing one of our products, requesting Services or information, or contacting us directly, we may ask you to provide some or all of the following types of information:Registering with SecureMac. When you purchase one of our products and use the Services, we may ask you for basic contact information (such as name, address, telephone number, email address), your credit card and/or billing information, your machine’s serial number and the license key associated with your purchase. Communications with Us. We may collect Personal Information from you such as email address, phone number or mailing address when you choose to request information about our Services, register for SecureMac’s mailing list, request to receive customer or technical support, or otherwise communicate with us.Surveys. From time to time, we may contact you to participate in online surveys. If you do decide to participate, you may be asked to provide certain information which may include Personal Information. All information collected from your participation in our surveys is provided by you voluntarily. We may use such information to improve our products, Sites and/or Services and in any manner consistent with the policies provided herein.Posting on the Site. SecureMac may offer publicly accessible pages, blogs, private messages, or community forums. You should be aware that, when you disclose information about yourself on SecureMac’s pages, blogs, private messages, and community forums, the Services will collect the information you provide in such submissions, including any Personal Information. If you choose to submit content to any public area of the Site, such content will be considered “public” and will not be subject to the privacy protections set forth herein.Automatic Data Collection. We may collect certain information automatically through our Services or other methods of web analysis, such as your Internet protocol (IP) address, cookie identifiers, and other device identifiers that are automatically assigned to your computer or device when you access the Internet, browser type and language, geo-location information, hardware type, operating system, Internet service provider, pages that you visit before and after using the Services, the date and time of your visit, the amount of time you spend on each page, information about the links you click and pages you view within the Services, and other actions taken through use of the Services such as preferences.Information Submitted Via the Services. You agree that SecureMac shall own and is free to use the content of any communications and related information submitted by you via the Services, including any feedback, bug reports, ideas, inventions, concepts, techniques, or know-how disclosed therein, for any purpose including developing, manufacturing, and/or marketing goods or Services. No compensation will be rendered for any information submitted via the Services. SecureMac is not required to acknowledge your name or attribute any information which you have provided via the Services to you. Information from Other Sources. We may receive information about you from other sources, including through Third-Party services and organizations to supplement information provided by you. For example, if you access our Services through a Third-Party application, such as an App Store or a social media site, we may collect information about you from that Third-Party application that you have made public via your privacy settings or that is necessary to facilitate the transaction. Information we collect from Third-Parties may include your name, location, sex, birth date, email, profile picture. This supplemental information allows us to verify information that you have provided to SecureMac and to enhance our ability to provide you with information about our business, products, and Services.  We may also obtain personal information about you from your general browsing activity.  Please see section 3.3 below.2. How SecureMac Uses Your InformationWe acquire, hold, use, and Process Personal Information about Individuals for a variety of business purposes, including: To Provide Products, Services, or Information Requested. SecureMac may use information about you to fulfill requests for products, provide the Services, or other information, including to:Generally manage Individual information and accounts;Process payment for products or services purchased;Respond to questions, comments, and other requests;Provide access to certain areas, functionalities, and features of SecureMac’s Services;Contact you to answer requests for customer support or technical support;Administrative Purposes. SecureMac may use Personal Information about you for its administrative purposes, including to:Measure interest in SecureMac’s Services;Develop new products and Services;Ensure internal quality control;Verify Individual identity and for fraud prevention;Communicate about Individual accounts and activities on SecureMac’s Services and systems, and, in SecureMac’s discretion, changes to any SecureMac policy;Send email to the email address you provide to us to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance;Process applications and transactions; Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities;Improve the effectiveness of our Site, our marketing endeavors, and our product or service offerings;Analyze and evaluate employment applications; andEnforce our Terms.Marketing SecureMac Products and Services. SecureMac may use Personal Information to provide you with materials about offers, products, and Services that may be of interest, including new content or Services. SecureMac may provide you with these materials by phone, postal mail, facsimile, or email, as permitted by applicable law. Such uses include:To tailor content, advertisements, and offers;To notify you about offers, products, and services that may be of interest to you;To provide Services to you and our sponsors;For other purposes disclosed at the time that Individuals provide Personal Information or as set forth elsewhere in this Privacy Policy; or Otherwise with your consent.You may contact us at any time to opt-out of the use of your Personal Information for marketing purposes, as further described in Section 6 below.Research and Development. SecureMac may use Personal Information alone or in the aggregate with information obtained from other sources, in order to help us to optimally deliver our existing products and Services or develop new products and Services. We may share anonymous Individual and aggregate data for research and analysis purposes.Direct Mail, Email and Outbound Telemarketing. Individuals who provide us with Personal Information, or whose Personal Information we obtain from Third Parties, may receive periodic emails, mailings, or phone calls from us with information on SecureMac’s or our business partners’ products and services or upcoming special offers/events we believe may be of interest. We offer the option to decline these communications at no cost to the Individual by following the instructions in Section 6 below.Anonymous and Aggregated Information Use. SecureMac may use Personal Information and other information about you to create anonymized and aggregated information, such as de-identified demographic information, de-identified location information, information about the computer or device from which you access SecureMac’s Services, or other analyses we create. Anonymized and aggregated information is used for a variety of functions, including the measurement of visitors’ interest in and use of various portions or features of the Services. Anonymized or aggregated information is not Personal Information, and SecureMac may use such information in a number of ways, including research, internal analysis, analytics, and any other legally permissible purposes. We may share this information within SecureMac and with Third Parties for our or their purposes in an anonymized or aggregated form that is designed to prevent anyone from identifying you.Sharing Content with Friends or Colleagues. SecureMac’s Services may offer various tools and functionalities. For example, SecureMac allows you to provide information about your friends through our referral services, such as “Tell a Friend.” Our referral services may allow you to forward or share certain content with a friend or colleague, such as an email inviting your friend to use our Services. Email addresses that you may provide for a friend or colleague will be used to send your friend or colleague the content or link you request, but will not be collected or otherwise used by SecureMac or any other Third Parties for any other purpose.Other Uses. SecureMac may use Personal Information for which we have a legitimate interest, such as direct marketing, network and information security, research (including marketing research), fraud prevention, disclosure to affiliated organizations, or any other purpose disclosed to you at the time you provide Personal Information or with your consent.3. Cookies, Pixel Tags/Web Beacons, Analytics Information, and Interest-Based AdvertisingWe, as well as Third Parties that provide content, advertising, or other functionality on our Services, may use cookies, pixel tags, local storage, and other technologies (“Technologies”) to automatically collect information through the Services. We use Technologies that are essentially small data files placed on your computer, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other devices (referred to collectively as a “Device“) that allow us to record certain pieces of information whenever you visit or interact with our Sites, Services, applications, messaging, and tools, and to recognize you across devices.Device Identifiers. When you visit or interact with our Site, you may provide us with information about your IP address, IDFA, Android/Google Advertising ID, IMEI, or other unique identifier.  We may also receive your Device location or other geolocation information, including the zip code, state or country from which you accessed the Site or the Services.Device Functionality.  During your visit, you may also provide information about your device, including your browser, browser language, operating system, hardware, and mobile network information. Cookies. Cookies are small text files placed in visitors’ computer browsers to store their preferences. Most browsers allow you to block and delete cookies. However, if you do that, the Site may not work properly.  Pixel Tags/Web Beacons. A pixel tag (also known as a web beacon) is a piece of code embedded on the Site that collects information about users’ engagement on that web page. The use of a pixel allows us to record, for example, that a user has visited a particular web page or clicked on a particular advertisement. We may also be able to see the pages you came from and pages you go to when you leave our Site (referring and exit web pages and URLs). Social Media Widgets: Our Site may include social media features such as the Facebook “Like” button and LinkedIn (that might include widgets such as the share this button or other interactive mini-programs). These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. These social media features are either hosted by a Third Party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.Analytics. We may also use Google Analytics and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to collect information regarding visitor behavior and visitor demographics on some of our Services, and to develop website content. This analytics data is not tied to any Personal Information. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You can opt out of Google’s collection and Processing of data generated by your use of the Services by going to http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Our uses of such Technologies fall into the following general categories:Operationally Necessary. We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies that are necessary to the operation of our Sites, Services, applications, and tools. This includes technologies that allow you access to our Sites, Services, applications, and tools; that are required to identify irregular site behavior, prevent fraudulent activity and improve security; or that allow you to make use of our functions such as shopping-carts, saved search, or similar functions;Performance Related. We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies to assess the performance of our Sites, applications, Services, and tools, including as part of our analytic practices to help us understand how our visitors use our websites, determine if you have interacted with our messaging, determine whether you have viewed an item or link, or to improve our website content, applications, Services, or tools;Functionality Related. We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies that allow us to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing or using our Sites, Services, applications, or tools. This may include identifying you when you sign into our Sites or keeping track of your specified preferences, interests, or past items viewed so that we may enhance the presentation of content on our Sites;Advertising or Targeting Related. We may use first-party or third-party cookies and web beacons to deliver content, including ads relevant to your interests, on our Sites or on third party sites. This includes using technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements and content that has been delivered to you, such as whether you have clicked on an advertisement.If you would like to opt-out of the Technologies we employ on our Sites, Services, applications, or tools, you may do so by blocking, deleting, or disabling them as your browser or device permits.4. Third-Party Websites and Social Media PlatformsThe Services may contain links to other websites and other websites may reference or link to our Site or other Services. These other domains and websites are not controlled by us, and SecureMac does not endorse or make any representations about Third-Party websites or social media platforms. We encourage our users to read the privacy policies of each and every website and application with which they interact. We do not endorse, screen or approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites or applications. Visiting these other websites or applications is at your own risk.SecureMac’s Services may include publicly accessible blogs, community forums, or private messaging features. The Site and our other Services may also contain links and interactive features with various social media platforms (e.g., widgets). If you already use these platforms, their cookies may be set on your device when using our Site or other Services. You should be aware that Personal Information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, chat room, social media platform or otherwise online, or that you share in an open forum may be viewed and used by others without any restrictions. We are unable to control such uses of your information when interacting with a social media platform, and by using such services you assume the risk that the Personal Information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties for any number of purposes.4. Third-Party Payment ProcessingWhen you make purchases through the Services, we process your payments through a Third-Party payment processor, including the Apple App Store. These Third-Party payment processors may collect certain financial information from you to process a payment on behalf of SecureMac, including your name, email address, address and other billing information.5. Human Resources DataSecureMac collects Personal Information from current, prospective, and former Employees, their contact points in case of a medical emergency, and beneficiaries under any insurance policy (“Human Resources Data”). The Human Resources Data we collect may include title, name, address, phone number, email address, date of birth, passport number, driver’s license number, Social Security number or other government-issued identification number, financial information related to credit checks, bank details for payroll, information that may be recorded on a CV or application form, language abilities, contact information of third parties in case of an emergency and beneficiaries under any insurance policy. We may also collect Sensitive Human Resources Data such as details of health and disability, including mental health, medical leave, and maternity leave; information about national origin or immigration status; and optional demographic information such as race, which helps us achieve our diversity goals.We acquire, hold, use and Process Human Resources Data for a variety of business purposes including:Workflow management, including assigning, managing and administering projects;Human Resources administration and communication;Payroll and the provision of benefits;Compensation, including bonuses and long-term incentive administration, stock plan administration, compensation analysis, including monitoring overtime and compliance with labor laws, and company recognition programs;Job grading activities;Performance and employee development management;Organizational development and succession planning;Benefits and personnel administration;Absence management;Helpdesk and IT support services;Regulatory compliance;Internal and/or external or governmental compliance investigations;Internal or external audits;Litigation evaluation, prosecution, and defense;Diversity and inclusion initiatives;Restructuring and relocation;Emergency contacts and services;Employee safety;Compliance with statutory requirements;Processing of Employee expenses and travel charges; andAcquisitions, divestitures, and integrations.5. Onward Transfer—SecureMac May Disclose Your Information1. Information We ShareWe may share your information as described in this Privacy Policy (e.g., with our Third-Party service providers; to comply with legal obligations; to protect and defend our rights and property) or with your permission.We Use Vendors and Service Providers. We may share any information we receive with vendors and service providers. The types of service providers (processors) to whom we entrust Personal Information include service providers for: (i) provision of IT and related services; (ii) provision of information and services you have requested; (iii) payment processing; (iv) customer service activities; and (v) in connection with the provision of the Services. SecureMac has executed appropriate contracts with the service providers that prohibit them from using or sharing Personal Information except as necessary to perform the contracted services on our behalf or to comply with applicable legal requirements.Business Partners. SecureMac may share Personal Information with our business partners, and affiliates for our and our affiliates’ internal business purposes or to provide you with a product or service that you have requested. SecureMac may also provide Personal Information to business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services, or whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. In such cases, our business partner’s name will appear, along with SecureMac. SecureMac requires our affiliates and business partners to agree in writing to maintain the confidentiality and security of Personal Information they maintain on our behalf and not to use it for any purpose other than the purpose for which SecureMac provided them.Displaying to Other Users. The content you post to the Services may be displayed on the Services. Other users of the Services may be able to see some information about you, such as your name if you submit a review, article, or a comment. We are not responsible for privacy practices of the other users who view or use information you post.Marketing – Interest-Based Advertising and Third-Party Marketing. Through our Services, SecureMac may allow Third-Party advertising partners to set tracking tools (e.g., cookies) to collect information regarding your activities (e.g., your IP address, page(s) visited, time of day). We may also share such de-identified information as well as selected Personal Information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) we have collected with Third-Party advertising partners. These advertising partners may use this information (and similar information collected from other websites) for purposes of delivering targeted advertisements to you when you visit non-SecureMac related websites within their networks. This practice is commonly referred to as “interest-based advertising” or “online behavioral advertising.” We may allow access to other data collected by the Services to facilitate transmittal of information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your Personal Information with Third-Party advertising partners, you may opt-out of such sharing at no cost by following the instructions in Section 6 below.Disclosures to Protect Us or Others (e.g., as Required by Law and Similar Disclosures). We may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information, other account information, and content if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to: (i) comply with law enforcement or national security requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (ii) respond to your requests; (iii) protect yours’, ours’ or others’ rights, property, or safety; (iv) to enforce SecureMac policies or contracts; (v) to collect amounts owed to SecureMac; (vi) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation or prosecution of suspected or actual illegal activity; or (vii) if we, in good faith, believe that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable.Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, then your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract. In such event, SecureMac will endeavor to direct the transferee to use Personal Information in a manner that is consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such Personal Information was collected.2. International Data TransfersYou agree that all Personal Information collected via or by SecureMac may be transferred, Processed, and stored anywhere in the world, including but not limited to, the United States, the European Union, in the cloud, on our servers, on the servers of our affiliates or the servers of our service providers in order to provide the Services. 6. Opt-Out (RIGHT TO OBJECT TO PROCESSING)1. GeneralYou may have the right to object to and opt out of certain uses and disclosures of your Personal Information. Where you have consented to SecureMac’s Processing of your Personal Information, you may withdraw that consent at any time and opt-out to further Processing by contacting privacy-request@securemac.com. Even if you opt-out, we may still collect and use non-Personal Information regarding your activities on our Services and/or information from the advertisements on Third-Party websites for non-interest based advertising purposes, such as to determine the effectiveness of the advertisements.2. Email and Telephone CommunicationsIf you receive an unwanted email from us, you can use the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email to opt-out of receiving future emails. We will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. Note that you will continue to receive transaction-related emails regarding products or services you have requested. We may also send you certain non-promotional communications regarding SecureMac and our Services and you will not be able to opt out of those communications (e.g., communications regarding updates to our EULA or this Privacy Policy).We maintain telephone “do-not-call” and “do-not-mail” lists as mandated by law. We process requests to be placed on do-not-mail, do-not-phone and do-not-contact lists within 60 days after receipt, or such shorter time as may be required by law.3. Mobile devicesSecureMac may occasionally send you push notifications through our mobile applications with notices that may be of interest to you. You may at any time opt-out from receiving these types of communications by changing the settings on your mobile device. SecureMac may also collect location-based information if you use our mobile applications. You may opt-out of this collection by changing the settings on your mobile device.4. Human Resources DataWith regard to Personal Information that SecureMac receives in connection with the employment relationship, SecureMac will use such Personal Information only for employment-related purposes as more fully described above. If SecureMac intends to use this Personal Information for any other purpose, SecureMac will notify the Individual and provide an opportunity to opt-out of such uses.5. “Do Not Track”Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. DNT is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services.  However, because there is no universally agreed-upon standard for what a company should do when it detects a DNT signal, currently we do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.6. Cookies and Interest-Based AdvertisingAs noted above, you may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs are not effective on mobile applications. However, on many mobile devices, application users may opt out of certain mobile ads via their device settings.To sign up for information or services with SecureMac or to download our software, you must have cookies enabled on your internet browser. Some of the more popular browsers (and links to manage your cookies on each) are:Internet Explorer FirefoxSafariGoogle ChromeIf you choose not to enable cookies, you will still be able to browse our Site, but it will restrict some of the functionality of our Site and what you can do. The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt-out of receiving targeted ads from our data partners and our other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You can access these, and also learn more about targeted advertising and consumer choice and privacy, at www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, or http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/ and www.aboutads.info/choices/. You can also choose not to be included in Google Analytics here.To be clear, whether you are using our opt-out or an online industry opt-out, these cookie-based opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For example, if you have opted-out on your computer browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt-out on each device. Advertisements on Third-Party websites that contain the AdChoices link and that link to this Privacy Policy may have been directed to you based on anonymous, non-Personal Information collected by advertising partners over time and across websites. These advertisements provide a mechanism to opt-out of the advertising partners’ use of this information for interest-based advertising purposes.7. Rights of Access, Rectification, Erasure, and RestrictionYou may inquire as to whether SecureMac is Processing Personal Information about you, request access to Personal Information, and ask that we correct, amend or delete your Personal Information where it is inaccurate. Where otherwise permitted by applicable law, you may send an e-mail to privacy-request@securemac.com or use any of the methods set out in this Privacy Policy to request access to, receive (port), seek rectification, or request erasure of Personal Information held about you by SecureMac. Please include your full name, email address associated with your Account, and a detailed description of your data request. Such requests will be processed in line with local laws.Although SecureMac makes good faith efforts to provide Individuals with access to their Personal Information, there may be circumstances in which SecureMac is unable to provide access, including but not limited to: where the information contains legal privilege, would compromise others’ privacy or other legitimate rights, where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the Individual’s privacy in the case in question, where the request is manifestly unfounded or excessive, or where it is commercially proprietary. If SecureMac determines that access should be restricted in any particular instance, we will provide you with an explanation of why that determination has been made and a contact point for any further inquiries. To protect your privacy, SecureMac will take commercially reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to or making any changes to your Personal Information.8. Data RetentionSecureMac retains the Personal Information we receive as described in this Privacy Policy for as long as you use our Services or as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected, provide our Services, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, conduct audits, pursue legitimate business purposes, enforce our agreements, and comply with applicable laws.9. Security of Your InformationWe incorporate commercially reasonable safeguards to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. We do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure.By using the Services or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Services. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Services or sending an e-mail to you. You may have a legal right to receive this notice in writing.10. Children’s PrivacyThis Site and the Services are not directed to children under 13 years of age, and SecureMac does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under 13 years of age.  Minors under the age of 16 (but older than 12) may use the Site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by these Terms and the Privacy Policy. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 13 (or under 16 in certain jurisdictions) who has provided his or her Personal Information, please contact us at privacy-request@securemac.com to request the deletion of such information.11. Redress/Compliance and AccountabilityIf you have any questions about our privacy practices, this Privacy Policy, or how to lodge a complaint with the appropriate authority, please contact SecureMac by email at privacy-request@securemac.com. We will address your concerns and attempt to resolve any privacy issues in a timely manner.12. Changes To Our Privacy Policy and PRacticesThis Privacy Policy may change from time to time. You understand and agree that you will be deemed to have accepted the updated Privacy Policy if you use the Services after the updated Privacy Policy is posted on the Services. If at any point you do not agree to any portion of the Privacy Policy then in effect, you must immediately stop using the Services.Revision to the Privacy Policy. We may revise this Privacy Policy in our sole discretion, so review it periodically. If you continue to visit this Site and use the services made available to you after such changes have been made, you hereby provide your consent to the changes.Posting of Revised Privacy Policy. If there are any material changes to this Privacy Policy, SecureMac will notify you by email or as otherwise required by applicable law. We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this web page, and the revised version will be effective immediately when it is posted (or upon notice as applicable). If you are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and read this Privacy Policy periodically. New Uses of Personal Information. Additionally, before we use Personal Information for any new purpose not originally authorized by you, we will endeavor to provide information regarding the new purpose and give you the opportunity to opt-out. Where consent of the Individual for the Processing of Personal Information is otherwise required by law or contract, SecureMac will endeavor to comply with the law or contract.13. DefinitionsThe following capitalized terms shall have the meanings herein as set forth below.“Agent” means any Third Party that Processes Personal Information pursuant to the instructions of, and solely for, SecureMac or to which SecureMac discloses Personal Information for use on its behalf.“Employee” refers to any current, temporary, permanent, prospective or former employee, director, contractor, worker, or retiree of SecureMac or its subsidiaries worldwide.“Personal Information” is any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (“Individual”).“Process” or “Processing” means any operation which is performed upon Personal Information, whether or not by automatic means, such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction.“Sensitive Data” or “Sensitive Personal Information” is a subset of Personal Information which, due to its nature, has been classified by law or by policy as deserving additional privacy and security protections. Sensitive Personal Information includes Personal Information regarding EU residents that is classified as a “Special Category of Personal Data” under EU law, which consists of the following data elements: (1) race or ethnic origin; (2) political opinions; (3) religious or philosophical beliefs; (4) trade union membership; (5) genetic data; (6) biometric data where Processed to uniquely identify a person; (6) health information; (7) sexual orientation or information about the Individual’s sex life; or (8) information relating to the commission of a criminal offense.“Third Party” is any company, natural or legal person, public authority, agency, or body other than the Individual, SecureMac or SecureMac’s Agents.14. YOUR California Privacy RightsAs described above, SecureMac collects certain types of personal information about your during your relationship with the company. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, SecureMac does not share Personal Information with Third Parties for their own marketing purposes.Under California law, if you are a resident of California, under certain circumstances, you have the right to request certain information that we collect about you, including:The categories of Personal Information we have collected from you; The categories of sources from which we collected the Personal Information; The business purpose we have for collecting or sharing that Personal Information; The categories of third parties with whom we share such Personal Information; andThe specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.In addition, you may request that we provide you with:The categories of Personal Information that we sold about you, and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold, by category or categories of Personal Information for each category of third parties to whom the information was sold; The categories of Personal Information that we have disclosed about you for a business purpose;  The category or categories of consumers’ Personal Information that we have sold, or if we have not sold consumers’ Personal Information; andThe category or categories of consumers’ Personal Information that we have disclosed for a business purpose, or if we have not disclosed that information for a business purpose. As a California resident, you also have the right, at any time, to tell us not to sell Personal Information – this is called the “right to opt-out” of the sale of Personal Information. In particular, our Site has collected the following categories of Personal Information from its consumers within the last twelve (12) months:
Category
Collected
A. Identifiers.
YES
B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)).
YES
C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law.
NO
D. Commercial information.
YES
E. Biometric information.
NO
F. Internet or other similar network activity.
YES
G. Geolocation data.
NO
H. Sensory data.
NO
I. Professional or employment-related information.
YES
J. Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)).
NO
K. Inferences drawn from other personal information.
YESFor purposes of the CCPA, Personal Information does not include:Publicly available information from government records.Deidentified or aggregated consumer information.Information excluded from the CCPA’s scope, like:health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data;personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Driver’s Privacy Protection Act of 1994.Please note that if we collected information about you for a single one-time transaction and do not keep that information in the ordinary course of business, that information will not be retained for purposes of a request under this section. In addition, if we have de-identified or anonymized data about you, we are not required to re-identify or otherwise link your identity to that data if it is not otherwise maintained that way in our records.You may make a written request to us at the contact information below to request this information. We may require you to confirm your identity and your residency in order to obtain the information, and you are only entitled to make this request twice a year. You may call, email or write us with your request at the contact information below. Please include “California Privacy Rights” as the subject line. You must include your full name, email address, and attest to the fact that you are a California resident by including a California postal address in your request. We will respond to your request within 45 days or let you know if we need additional time.Email Address:privacy-request@securemac.comPostal Address:SecureMac, Inc. 1930 Village Center Circle 3-369 Las Vegas, Nevada 89134We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:Deny you goods or services.Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.However, we may offer you certain financial incentives permitted by the CCPA that can result in different prices, rates, or quality levels. Any CCPA-permitted financial incentive we offer will reasonably relate to your personal information’s value and contain written terms that describe the program’s material aspects. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt in consent, which you may revoke at any time.15. Your nevada privacy rightsIf you are a Nevada resident, you have the right to request certain information from us regarding the collection and sale of your personal information (as defined in Nevada Revised Statutes 603A.320) during your visit to our websites or when you otherwise interact with us online. If you have sought or acquired, by purchase or lease, any goods or services for personal, family, or household purposes from the Uninterrupted Site, you may ask us to disclose whether we have sold (for monetary consideration) certain information about you (including your first and last name, physical address, email address, telephone number, social security number, an identifier that allows you to be contacted either physically or online, or other contact information that allows us to identify you personally). As a Nevada resident, you may also request to opt out of us sharing such information about you.  To make this inquiry, please submit a request in writing to privacy-request@securemac.com with “Nevada Privacy Rights” in the subject line. You must include your full name, email address, and attest that you are a Nevada resident by providing a Nevada postal address in your request. Please state whether you are requesting information and/or opting out.We will process your request within 60 days, or we will let you know if we need additional time. We may require additional information to verify your identity before we can respond.16. Revision history
Title (Effective Date)
SecureMac Privacy Policy                      Effective: 2/21/2017
Updated SecureMac Privacy Policy       Effective:  1/1/2020Want to become a Partner?Learn more about becoming a SecureMac Partner or joining our affiliate program today! Become a Partner Join the Affiliate ProgramJoin our mailing list for the latest security news and deals
×
